ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Legal Department [2 of 3], 1977 (Box 181, Folder 10)
- Legal Department [3 of 3], 1974-1976 (Box 181, Folder 11)
- Memos, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 1)
- Managers Meetings, 1973-1975 (Box 182, Folder 2)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 3)
- Multi Fiber Arrangement, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 4)
- Multilateral Trade Negotiations, 1977-1980 (Box 182, Folder 5)
- National Energy Coalition, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  March 2, April 1 and 6
- National Labor Relations Board and Act, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 7)
- National Recycling Coalition, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 8)
- National Security Studies, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 9)
- Negro Trade Union, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 10)
- New America, 1974-1977 (Box 182, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Guild of New York, 1973-1977 (Box 182, Folder 12)
- New York City Council on Economic Education, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 13)
- New York Clothing Unemployment Fund Agency, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 14)
- The New York Club International Association, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 15)
  February 3 and 9
- New York Hospital Cornell Medical Center, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 16)
- Northwestern University, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 17)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1973-1977 (Box 182, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Organizing Retail, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 19)
  September 20
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Organizing Service and Allied Industries Joint Board, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 20)
  February 18 and 22
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Organizing Southwest, 1975-1976 (Box 182, Folder 21)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration: Copies of Laws, Proceedings and Other Printed Matter, 1973-1977 (Box 182, Folder 22)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 23)
- Organizing Department, 1977-1978 (Box 182, Folder 24)
- Political Action Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 182, Folder 25)
- Canadian Political Action Contributions, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 26)
- Political Education Department, 1977-1978 (Box 182, Folder 27)
- Public Relations Department, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 28)
- Public Relations Department [2 of 2], 1973-1977 (Box 182, Folder 29)
- Public Contracts (State Legislation), 1977 (Box 182, Folder 30)
- Public Employment Relations Board (PERB), 1977-1978 (Box 182, Folder 31)
- Ratner Corporation, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 32)
- Raven Industries, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 33)
  February 6
- Dixie Lee Ray Governor, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 34)
  December 23
- Recruitment Training Program, 1977-1978 (Box 182, Folder 35)
- Regional Plan Association Conference, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 36)
- Amalgamated Social Benefits Association: Chicago, 1977-1978 (Box 183, Folder 1)
- Howard Samuel, 1974-1977 (Box 183, Folder 2)
- Seinsheimer Company, 1973-1977 (Box 183, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings on Capital Formation, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 4)
- Senate Subcommittee on Citizens and Shareholders Rights and Remedies, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 5)
- Senate Select Committee on Small Business, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 6)
- Service Employees International Union, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 7)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1975-1978 (Box 183, Folder 8)
- Social Democrats, United States of America, 1973-1979 (Box 183, Folder 9)
- Social Security, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 10)
- Social Services Department, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union, 1976-1978 (Box 183, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Social Welfare Program, 1975 (Box 183, Folder 12)
  March 7
- National Planning Association (NPA) [1 of 2], 1976 (Box 183, Folder 13)
- National Planning Association (NPA) [2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 183, Folder 14)
- Society of Professionals in Dispute Resolutions, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 15)
  October 29 through November 1
- Southern Department, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union, 1975-1978 (Box 183, Folder 16)
- South West Voter Registration Education Project, 1974-1975 (Box 183, Folder 17)
- Staff Conference, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 18)
- Staff Education Conference held in Saint Louis, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 19)
  December 5 through 8
- State Political Action Fund (SPAF), 1973-1976 (Box 183, Folder 20)
- Stanley Steingut, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 21)
- Sol Stetin: Non Active, 1977-1979 (Box 183, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens, 1980 (Box 183, Folder 23)
  December 11
- T Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box 183, Folder 24)
- Tailored Clothing Industry Proposal, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 25)
  June 21
- Target Sportswear, 1975-1976 (Box 184, Folder 1)
- Task Force Economic Development New York State: Labor/Management Conference Buffalo, 1975 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  November 6
- Task Force: Impact of National Health Insurance, 1977 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  February 2 and July 11
- Textile Appeals, 1977 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  March 21 and June 29
- Textile: Bag and Packaging, 1975-1977 (Box 184, Folder 5)
- Textile: Benefit Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 184, Folder 6)
- Textile: Canadian Conference Quebec City, 1977 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  April 25
- Complaints and Grievances (Textile), 1976-1977 (Box 184, Folder 8)
- Textile Financial, 1976 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  June 2
- Textile Division: General Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 184, Folder 10)
- Textile Division: Health Plan (Box 184, Folder 11)
- Textile Division: Joint Board Offices, 1976-1978 (Box 184, Folder 12)
- Textile: Industrial Engineering Department, 1976-1977 (Box 184, Folder 13)
- Textile Native: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union, 1976 (Box 184, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union: Textile Division Organizing, 1976-1977 (Box 184, Folder 15)
- Textile Staff Retirement Plan, 1976-1978 (Box 184, Folder 16)
- Strike Benefits Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union (Textile), 1977 (Box 184, Folder 17)
  April 1
- Textile Workers' Voice, 1977 (Box 184, Folder 18)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1975-1978 (Box 184, Folder 19)
- Trade (International): Trade Department, 1977-1978 (Box 184, Folder 20)
- Trade Study, 1978 (Box 184, Folder 21)
  April 19
- Trade Negotiations Advisory Council, 1975-1978 (Box 184, Folder 22)
- Gundersheim Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 185, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 185, Folder 2)
- Gundersheim Correspondence [1 of 5], 1990 (Box 185, Folder 3)
- Gundersheim Correspondence [2 of 5], 1989 (Box 185, Folder 4)
- Gundersheim Correspondence [3 of 5], 1989 (Box 185, Folder 5)
- Gundersheim Correspondence [4 of 5], 1988 (Box 185, Folder 6)
- Arthur Gundersheim, 1988-1991 (Box 185, Folder 7)
- Gundersheim Correspondence [5 of 5], 1988 (Box 185, Folder 7)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance Petition, 1986-1996 (Box 185, Folder 8)
- Martin Blouse Company, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  December 10
- Martin Shirt Company, Incorporated, 1985-1988 (Box 185, Folder 10)
- Karg Brothers, Incorporated, 1990-1991 (Box 185, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1985-1989 (Box 185, Folder 12)
- Complaints: Slobodzian, Thelma, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 1)
- Complaints: October, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 2)
- Complaints: September, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 3)
- Complaints: August, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 4)
- Complaints: March, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 5)
- Complaints: July, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 6)
- Complaints: June, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 7)
- Complaints: May, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 8)
- Complaints: April, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 9)
- Complaints: January, 1992 (Box 186, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous [1 of 2], 1987-1990 (Box 186, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous [1 of 2], 1988-1991 (Box 186, Folder 12)
- Theresa Meixner, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 1)
- Morgan Shirt Company: Morgantown, West Virginia, 1988-1989 (Box 187, Folder 2)
- Viola Milano, 1987-1988 (Box 187, Folder 3)
- James Mathieu, Junior Esquire, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 4)
- Martha Division, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  August 18
- Helen Malits (John Fox), 1985 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  June 11 and 12
- Dorothy Mack, 1985 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  April 23
- George Mozzanica, 1986-1987 (Box 187, Folder 8)
- Mary Waddell and Marilyn Matier, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 9)
- James McGinnis, 1986-1989 (Box 187, Folder 10)
- Dixie McKee, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 11)
  October 1 and November 24
- George McGuire, Junior, 1985-1987 (Box 187, Folder 12)
- Larue Norton, 1990-1991 (Box 187, Folder 13)
- Frank Niebolte, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 14)
- Dolores Natale, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 15)
- Donald Oester, 1987-1988 (Box 187, Folder 16)
- Mike Oney, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 17)
  January 5 and 21
- Roger Pollard, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 18)
- Faye Prescott, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 19)
  January 31
- Peggy Palmer, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 20)
- Robina Patterson, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 21)
  May 25 and June 27
- Cosimina Torraco, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 22)
- Mary Phillips, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 23)
- Ruby Patterson, 1984-1987 (Box 187, Folder 24)
- Victoria Payne, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 25)
- Roland Partlow, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 26)
- Jerome Petrillo, 1987-1988 (Box 187, Folder 27)
- Linda Poarch, 1986-1987 (Box 187, Folder 28)
- George Puntieri, 1988 (Box 187, Folder 29)
  May 3
- Genetta Robertson, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 30)
- Elizabeth Roberson, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 31)
  December 26 and 27
- Aimee Rathburn, 1990-1991 (Box 187, Folder 32)
- Ruth Ann Ross, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 33)
- Bruce Raynor, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 34)
- George Roth, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 35)
- Clander Roberts, 1988 (Box 187, Folder 36)
- Rose Radon, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 37)
  April 6 and 15
- Ester Remillard, 1985 (Box 187, Folder 38)
  April 23 and May 2
- Barbara Revelle, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 39)
- Jeanette Rogers, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 40)
  August 1
- Ronald David Renfroe, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 41)
- Garland Smith, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 42)
  October 17 and November 1
- Mary Ann Ritchey Sciranko, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 43)
  August 1 and September 5
- Loretha Stephens, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 44)
- Carmela Sabbatini, 1989-1990 (Box 187, Folder 45)
- Annabelle Shoemaker, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 46)
- Barbara Sebra, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 47)
  July 1 and August 20
- Marta Samano, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 48)
- Karen Stubbins, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 49)
  September 30
- Rita Sielers, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 50)
- Donna Stull, 1985 (Box 187, Folder 51)
  April 21 and May 6
- Louise Sullivan, 1985 (Box 187, Folder 52)
- Betty Sanders, 1984-1985 (Box 187, Folder 53)
- Brenda Skaggs, 1985-1986 (Box 187, Folder 54)
- Mary Skurnick, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 55)
- Lonnie Smeed, 1988 (Box 187, Folder 56)
- Suzanne Shuniak Local 653, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 57)
  November 6, 21 and 22
- Roy Svoboda, 1987-1988 (Box 187, Folder 58)
- Pausy Schneider, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 59)
- Irene Trail, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 60)
- Jeannette Thomas, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 61)
- Maria Torres, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 62)
  May 1 and 9
- Jaimi Torres, 1986-1988 (Box 187, Folder 63)
- Norma Tuschhoff, 1985 (Box 187, Folder 64)
- Mary Trammell, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 65)
- Elsie Trembley, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 66)
- Dolores Turkovich, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 67)
- Flora Villazon, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 68)
  July 30
- Julio Velazquez, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 69)
  September 15 and 18
- Dorothy Sue White, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 70)
  April 29 and May 31
- Ollie Wilson, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 71)
- Joyce Watson, 1989-1990 (Box 187, Folder 72)
- Helen Weissman, 1989-1990 (Box 187, Folder 73)
- Barbara Winfrey, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 74)
- Warren White, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 75)
- Herbert Walder, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 76)
  December 24
- Emma Weber, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 77)
  April 22
- Early Ward, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 78)
- Leona Ward, 1987-1988 (Box 187, Folder 79)
- Roger Ward Local 2408, 1987-1988 (Box 187, Folder 80)
- Margaret Wanamaker, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 81)
- Dan Walter, 1987 (Box 187, Folder 82)
- Charles Wetzel, 1985 (Box 187, Folder 83)
- Dorothy Sue White, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 84)
  December 4
- Michael Wilber Local 1280A, 1985 (Box 187, Folder 85)
  July 25 and August 5
- Edward Wyatt, 1986 (Box 187, Folder 86)
  February 19 and 20
- Complaints: December, 1993 (Box 187, Folder 87)
- Local 1044, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  March 11 and April 10
- Members of Local 95, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  May 23 and 31
- Members of Local 1355, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 3)
- Local 1355, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  March 7 and April 10
- Local 1093T, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  November 12
- Members of Local 56A, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  February 15 and 20
- Local 630, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  October 15 and November 19
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board (Carmen Papale), 1991 (Box 188, Folder 8)
- New England Regional Joint Board (Steve Stycos), 1990 (Box 188, Folder 9)
- Local 1374, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 10)
- Local 744, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 11)
- Local 903, 1989-1990 (Box 188, Folder 12)
- Local 146, 1985-1986 (Box 188, Folder 13)
- Local 841, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 14)
  April 14
- Local 365, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 15)
  August 5
- Local 2308, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 16)
  June 26 and July 8
- Local 1077, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 17)
  June 25 and July 8
- Local 33T, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 18)
- Local 694, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 19)
- Local 1099, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 20)
- Local 976, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 21)
- Local 606, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 22)
- Alfredo Arroyo, 1995 (Box 188, Folder 23)
  November 9
- Aleda Anderson, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 24)
- Doris Alvey, 1989-1990 (Box 188, Folder 25)
- Brenda Able, 1983-1985 (Box 188, Folder 26)
- Josephine Andrews, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 27)
  September 4 and 9
- Bonnie Adkins, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 28)
  February 27
- Leticia Alvarez, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 29)
  September 3 and 30
- Hazel Armentroub, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 30)
- Frankie Brice, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 31)
  November 1
- Muriel Brown, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 32)
- Batesville Casket Company, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 33)
- Jackie Burden, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 34)
- Phoebe Bringle, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 35)
- Irene Baker, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 36)
- Nunzio Betto, 1988-1989 (Box 188, Folder 37)
- Margaret Baudendistel, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 38)
  April 23 and 26
- Belinda Bender, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 39)
  March 14
- Clara Bryant, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 40)
- Carol Baney, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 41)
- Lucille Barrett, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 42)
- James Bester, 1987-1988 (Box 188, Folder 43)
- Lillie Brooks, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 44)
- Marvin Bailey, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 45)
  October 2 and 8
- Aloyzina Bochnoch, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 46)
  April 8 and 15
- Lucy Bode, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 47)
  February 15
- Ruth Bradley, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 48)
- Teresa Brown, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 49)
- Carolyn Butz, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 50)
- Donald Conover, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 51)
- Troy Crumpton, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 52)
- Marie Cheshire, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 53)
  February 2 and 20
- Juana Crespo, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 54)
- Bud Clark Local 1899, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 55)
- Billie Chumley, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 56)
- Joseph Corvino, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 57)
- Brenda Covey, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 58)
  June 5 and 13
- Clarence Clarke, 1982-1984 (Box 188, Folder 59)
- Mary Cacucciolo, 1985-1986 (Box 188, Folder 60)
- Mary Cunningham, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 61)
- Milfred Champion, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 62)
- Frank Clayton, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 63)
- Clara Cobb, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 64)
  July 10
- Henry Dropkin, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 65)
  June 10 and July 15
- Karon Dickerson, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 66)
  September 5
- Carl McKinley Dixon Junior, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 67)
  March 30 and April 2
- Debra Dockins, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 68)
  January 22 and 31
- Olivia Dorsey, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 69)
  December 7
- James Dozier, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 70)
- Ammon Dearment, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 71)
- Sally Didonna, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 72)
  June 12
- Barbara Davis, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 73)
- Derossi and Son Company, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 74)
- Margherita De Leo, 1987-1988 (Box 188, Folder 75)
- Donna Demers, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 76)
- Cecelia Deuser, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 77)
- Donna Degraide, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 78)
- Geraldine Dorwart (Sam Carita), 1983-1986 (Box 188, Folder 79)
- Heather Duran, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 80)
- Betty Edwards, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 81)
- Masada Ebeid, 1985-1986 (Box 188, Folder 82)
- Ida Evard, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 83)
  March 28 and 31
- Carmen Estremera, 1986-1987 (Box 188, Folder 84)
- Reyna Ferriera, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 85)
- Janet Frederick, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 86)
- Nina Firestone, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 87)
  July 17
- Laura Farmer New, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 88)
- Bobby Farmer, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 89)
- Dominic Fulginiti, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 90)
- M. Fine and Sons, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 91)
- Doris Goods, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 92)
- Birute Gintvaninis, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 93)
- Joseph Grosso, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 94)
  June 29 and July 19
- Barbara Goalsley, 1989-1990 (Box 188, Folder 95)
- James Gebhard, 1986-1987 (Box 188, Folder 96)
- Anthony Giordano, 1983-1985 (Box 188, Folder 97)
- Tammua Ann Gondek, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 98)
- Louise Graham, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 99)
- Christle Hogue, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 100)
- Sue Hicks, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 101)
- Georgia Hoffman, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 102)
- Shirley Hepfl, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 103)
- Kathleen Hensley, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 104)
- Ann Hammonds, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 105)
  July 20
- Martha Hicks, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 106)
- Ronald Holgash, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 107)
  July 19
- Florence Bradform Haimowitz, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 108)
- Eveline Hensley, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 109)
- Raymond C. Henley, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 110)
- Margaret Houston, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 111)
- Rosemary Ibaria (Bill Gomez), 1986 (Box 188, Folder 112)
- Daisy B. Irvin, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 113)
- William Jackson, 1989-1990 (Box 188, Folder 114)
- Arzo Jones, Jr., B. Raynor, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 115)
- Arzo Jones Jr., 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 116)
- Joe T. Jones, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 117)
- Chew Jin, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 118)
- Florence Johnson, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 119)
- Beverly Johnson, 1989-1990 (Box 188, Folder 120)
- Mary Jasson, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 121)
- Jo Sportswear, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 122)
- Shane Klein, Pres. Troytown Manuf. B. Towne, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 123)
- Maria Karambela - LCL 400 T. Rumore, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 124)
- Thomas E. Kendrick, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 125)
- Cecilia Krempasky (John Fox), 1985 (Box 188, Folder 126)
- John Kermondy (G. Ferraris), 1981-1985 (Box 188, Folder 127)
- Barbara King (A. Loevy), 1985 (Box 188, Folder 128)
- Nancy Kirby, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 129)
- Carol Liptock, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 130)
- Lewistown Area, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 131)
- A. Langeven, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 132)
- R. Lynn Kyle, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 133)
- Marie Lowery, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 134)
- Sweetie Lundy, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 135)
- Donna Lapp, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 136)
- Tom Loehrer, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 137)
- Edward Lorenchik, 1985 (Box 188, Folder 138)
- Basil T. Madjoucoff, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 139)
- Victoria Magallanes, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 140)
- Beulah M. Moore, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 141)
- Jeanne Merlino, 1989-1990 (Box 188, Folder 142)
- Beulah M. Moore, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 143)
- Carla Martinelli, 1989 (Box 188, Folder 144)
- Darlene Mulhollen, 1989-1990 (Box 188, Folder 145)
- Sub Sahara Africa, 1978 (Box 189, Folder 1)
- Argentina, 1983-1996 (Box 189, Folder 2)
- Bulgaria, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 3)
- Canada, 1979-1981 (Box 189, Folder 4)
- Chile, 1978-1979 (Box 189, Folder 5)
- China, 1985 (Box 189, Folder 6)
- Costa Rica, 1993 (Box 189, Folder 7)
- Dominican Republic, 1988-1989 (Box 189, Folder 8)
- El Salvador, 1989 (Box 189, Folder 9)
- Guatemala, 1977-1988 (Box 189, Folder 10)
- Haiti, 1982 (Box 189, Folder 11)
- Hong Kong, 1979-1984 (Box 189, Folder 12)
- Hungary, 1982-1983 (Box 189, Folder 13)
- Italy, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 14)
- Israel, 1982-1993 (Box 189, Folder 15)
- Japan, 1977-1985 (Box 189, Folder 16)
- Korea, 1977-1996 (Box 189, Folder 17)
- Mariana Islands, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 18)
- Mauritius, 1983-1985 (Box 189, Folder 19)
- Philippines, 1981-1989 (Box 189, Folder 20)
- Peru, 1982 (Box 189, Folder 21)
- Romania, 1976-1977 (Box 189, Folder 22)
- South Africa, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 23)
- Arthur Gundersheim, 1992-1995 (Box 189, Folder 24)
- Ron Blackwell, 1992-1995 (Box 189, Folder 25)
- AD: Purchases, 1992-1993 (Box 189, Folder 26)
- AD: ACTWU: History (Box 189, Folder 27)
- AD: Biography: JS, 1985 (Box 189, Folder 28)
- AD Budgets, 1993 (Box 189, Folder 29)
- ACTWU General Board Meeting, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 30)
- ACTWU - Manhattan, 1984 (Box 189, Folder 31)
- ACTN - Advisory Committee on Trade Negotiations, 1982-1989 (Box 190, Folder 1)
- ACTWU - General, 1983-1990 (Box 190, Folder 2)
- ACTWU F.o.u.r. Contracts, 1985-1990 (Box 190, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Unemployed Members, 1983 (Box 190, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1984-1995 (Box 190, Folder 5)
- Clothing Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 190, Folder 6)
- Footwear 201, 1985 (Box 190, Folder 7)
- Footwear 201, 1985 (Box 190, Folder 8)
- Footwear 201 - 1985 Case (Box 191, Folder 1)
- Footwear 301 Case, 1982-1984 (Box 191, Folder 2)
- Footwear Coalition, 1982-1983 (Box 191, Folder 3)
- Footwear Files, 1985 (Box 191, Folder 4)
- Footwear CUD Case, 1983 (Box 191, Folder 5)
- Footwear 301 Case 1984, 1986 (Box 191, Folder 6)
- Footwear Files, 1985 (Box 191, Folder 7)
- GATT- General Agreements on Tariffs and Trade, 1981-1993 (Box 191, Folder 8)
- Group of 33, 1985-1987 (Box 191, Folder 9)
- GSP File, 1987-1992 (Box 191, Folder 10)
- GSP 1988 Review, 1986-1988 (Box 192, Folder 1)
- GSP, 1987 (Box 192, Folder 2)
- GSP Subcommittee Foreign Correspondence, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  [Folder 1 of 2]
- GSP Subcommittee Foreign Correspondence, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  [Folder 2 of 2]
- Generalized System of Preferences Trade Policy Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 192, Folder 5)
- FITITVC: Free Trade Zone, 1990 (Box 192, Folder 6)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1976 (Box 192, Folder 7)
- Labor-Industry Coalition for International Trade, 1990-1991 (Box 192, Folder 8)
- Labor-Industry Coalition for International Trade, 1984-1986 (Box 192, Folder 9)
- LICIT Briefing Book, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 10)
- LICIT Attitude Study, 1988 (Box 192, Folder 11)
- Leather Apparel, 1980-1983 (Box 193, Folder 1)
- American Fiber/Textile/Apparel Coalition Legal Case 3, 1983-1984 (Box 193, Folder 2)
- Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 193, Folder 3)
- MLTAC Meeting Notes, 1984 (Box 193, Folder 4)
- Management-Labor Textile Advisory List, 1980-1983 (Box 193, Folder 5)
- LICIT Proposed Changes, 1990 (Box 193, Folder 6)
- Canada Wool Apparel, 1995 (Box 193, Folder 7)
- Canada Labor Congress, 1990 (Box 193, Folder 8)
- US Canadian Free Trade Agreement, 1989 (Box 193, Folder 9)
- US Canadian Free Trade Agreement, 1989 (Box 193, Folder 10)
- Canadian Free Trade Negotiations, 1988 (Box 193, Folder 11)
- Canadian Free Trade, 1988 (Box 193, Folder 12)
- Canadian Free Trade, 1988 (Box 193, Folder 13)
- Canadian Free Trade, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  [Folder 1 of 3]
- Canadian Free Trade, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  [Folder 2 of 3]
- Canadian Free Trade, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  [Folder 3 of 3]
- Advisory Committee for Trade Policy and Negotiations, 1992 (Box 194, Folder 4)
- North American Free Trade Agreement, 1993 (Box 194, Folder 5)
- Advisory Committee for Trade Policy and Negotiations, 1992 (Box 194, Folder 6)
- Citizens Trade Watch Campaign, 1989 (Box 194, Folder 7)
- North American Free Trade Agreement, 1993 (Box 194, Folder 8)
- North American Free Trade Agreement, 1995 (Box 194, Folder 9)
- United States International Trade Commission, 1993 (Box 194, Folder 10)
- Impact of NAFTA, 1989-1995 (Box 194, Folder 11)
- NAFTA Remarks, 1992 (Box 194, Folder 12)
- Highlights on NAFTA, 1992 (Box 194, Folder 13)